You won!
(Penny:)Certainly doesn't
feel like it, does it?
(Dr Koothrappali:)You know, my wife used to throw
(Dr Koothrappali:)theme parties like this
all the time.
(Penny:)Oh, I guess that's
where Raj gets it from.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Well, he and his mother
spent a lot of time together
(Dr Koothrappali:)when he was young.
(Dr Koothrappali:)I was always working.
(Penny:)Hey, you know, Raj is dating
(Penny:)a doctor who works a lot.
(chuckles)
(Penny:)Him and his mom have a type.
You g... Y-You got to laugh
at that, right?
(Penny:)No? All right.
(Santa:)All right, let me see
if I've got this straight.
(Santa:)A picture of you on my lap
(Santa:)is a way to punish
your girlfriend
(Santa:)for making you
celebrate Christmas?
(Sheldon:)Correct.